bechna.com 2017-05-24

# Privacy Policy | Bechna Classifieds

http://www.Bechna.com 

Effective from 10th of January 2012 to 10th of January 2013.

* * *

General Information

Bechna takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following information to learn more about our privacy practices.

  * This policy covers what personally identifiable information Bechna collects and how it is treated. Personally identifiable information is information that can be used to identify visitors to the http://www.bechna.com Web Site. This information may be limited to an IP address or extend to personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address, or phone number.
  * This policy only applies to http://www.bechna.com and does not extend to the practices of other Web Sites that we may link to, companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage.

* * *

Contact Information

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this privacy policy.

Our Internet address is located at [http://www.bechna.com](http://www.magicdoormat.com/)

You may contact us by e-mail using our contact form http://bechna.com/help/contact 

* * *

Dispute Resolution

Bechna is committed to resolving any dispute you may have regarding our privacy policy quickly and efficiently.

Disputes will be handled by our customer service representative. Our customer service will promptly correct any errors.

* * *

Information Collection

When visiting Web Sites certain information about you and your computer can sometimes be collected. This section explains what information Bechna collects, and how it is used.

Information Collected – What information do we collect and why? 
We collect the following identifiable information about our visitors: 
Global area of Web Site 

      * dynamic.clickstream
      * dynamic.http
      * dynamic.searchtext
      * dynamic.miscdata area 

Blog area of Web Site

      * dynamic.clickstream
      * dynamic.http
      * dynamic.searchtext
      * dynamic.miscdata

We collect identifiable information for the following reasons:

Global area of Web Site 

      * Web Site and System Administration 

area of Web Site

      * No Identifiable Information Collected 

Blog area of Web Site

      * Web Site and System Administration

Collecting your address information will allow us to deliver your goods efficiently.

Our Web Site generates server log files automatically. These log files are used to generate statistical information and error reports to ensure the Web Site runs with a minimum of disruption. They are not actively used to identify individual visitors.

* * *

Information Recipients – Who has access to the information collected?

Global area of Web Site 

      * Ourselves and/or our entities acting as our agents or entities for which we are acting as an agent. 

area of Web Site

      * No Identifiable Information Collected 

Blog area of Web Site

      * Ourselves and/or our entities acting as our agents or entities for which we are acting as an agent.

* * *

Information Retention – How long is this information retained?

Global area of Web Site 

      * We do not have a retention policy for this area of the Web Site. 

area of Web Site

      * No Identifiable Information Collected 

Blog area of Web Site

      * We do not have a retention policy for this area of the Web Site.

* * *
